I never dreamed before
（コユキ）ダメだ…
I'm gonna knock the door
こんな難しいの 覚えられません
into the world of perfect free
（コユキ）無理です
(You ain't no lonely!)
（ペイジ）アホーッ
You're gonna say I'm lying
（斎藤(さいとう)）ん～ でもねぇ—
I'm gonna get the chance
スケールは早めに覚えといたほうが
いいんだけどな
I thought a chance is far from me
アホーッ
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
このバカ鳥め！ 鳴かせてやる！
(I was made to hit in America)
I was made to hit in America
プイッ ギョ～ ギョギョギョ…
You are the sun, you are the star
う… ハァ…
(To me, forever)
You are the sun, you are the star
ハハハハ…
焦っちゃダメだよ コユキ君
(To me, forever)
まだギターを手にして
２か月ちょっとなんだから
（ペイジ）
クワー！ ギョギョギョ…
（コユキ）でも あいつは…
I was made to hit in America
もう… スケールなんか…
（ペイジ）クワ～！ ギョギョ…
ほらほら
気分転換に泳ぎに行くぞ～
(I was made to hit in America)
I was made to hit in America
（ペイジ）ギャ～ギュ ギャ～ギュ
(I was made to hit in America)
I was made to hit in America
"C-Major Pentatonic Scale"
It's no good. I can't learn this.
It's too hard for me.
Fool!
But it's better to learn the scale early.
You stupid bird! I'll show you!
Don't rush it, Koyuki-kun.
It's only been two months
since you started playing the guitar.
But he already knows the scale...
C'mon, we need a change of pace.
Let's go swimming!
Huh?!
"Lucille"
-Okay, here goes!
-Watch the ball!
（部員１）うわっ
（部員２）ああ… わっ
What?
（兵藤(ひょうどう)）何だと？
（部員２）ん？
Umm...So please buy your own melon roll.
（コユキ）あの… だから
メロンパンは自分で買ってきてよ
It's the truth. I was called
to the faculty office.
マジ 俺
今 職員室に呼ばれてるから…
（兵藤）ふーん…
S-see you...
（コユキ）そ そんじゃ
（兵藤）待てよ 田中
Hold it, Tanaka!
（アナウンス）
２年４組の田中幸雄君—
Yukio Tanaka of Grade 8B.
Please go to the
faculty office immediately. I repeat...
至急 職員室に来てください
繰り返します…
Listen, Tanaka-kun...
（桃子(ももこ)）あのさあ 田中君…
I don't think you're taking your job
as umbrella monitor seriously.
（桃子）田中君って
傘係の仕事ナメてるでしょ？
えっ いや そんな…
Huh? Oh, no...
こういう小さなことの
積み重ねなんだよ
Daily life is a series
of little jobs like this.
生活習慣っていうのは
Maybe I should put this
in your student report...
内申書に書こうかな…
ガッカリしたな 田中君には
I'm disappointed in you, Tanaka-kun.
もう行っていいわよ
You may go.
Wait, Tanaka-kun!
ちょっと 田中君！
What is this?!
何これ？
What happened?!
どうしたの？
Oh...It's nothing.
（コユキ）あ… 大丈夫です
We were kidding around
and Tanabe-kun did a drop kick on me.
ふざけてて—
田辺(たなべ)君にドロップキックを
もらっちゃったんです
田中君…
Tanaka-kun...
And naturally, I gave it
back to him with a heel hold!
（コユキ）もちろん 僕も
ヒールホールドで返したんで—
So it's no big deal!
別に 何も…
Tanaka-kun...
田中君…
-Did you catch that game?
-Yeah! That was awesome!
（男子生徒１）
お前 きのう横浜(よこはま)の試合見た？
（男子生徒２）あー 見た
あれすごかったな ハハハッ
（男子生徒１）スタンドにいたよ～
前のヤツ面白かったじゃん
（コユキ）ハァ…
（真帆(まほ)）元気ないぞ コユキ
You look glum, Koyuki!
ん？ 真帆！
Maho!
Yo!
Maho, you sure eat a lot.
真帆って よく食べるね
Huh?
Shut up. I'm hungry.
うるさいなぁ
おなかすいてんだよっ
You'll gain weight.
（コユキ）太るよ
You can have my fries.
（真帆）ポテト 食べてもいいよ
Beck's first live performance has been set!
決まったよ！ BECK(ベック)の初ライブ！
Huh?! R-really?
そ… そう
How long is this going to continue?
いつまで こんな状態続けるの？
私が話してあげるよ
I'll talk to him for you.
Okay...
Okay, I'm going on deliveries,
（斎藤）それじゃ 僕は
配達してくるんでコユキ君は—
so make up for being late
and work extra hard.
遅れてきた分も
みっちり働くように！
I'm sorry!
（コユキ）すみませんでした
And don't forget to feed Page.
（斎藤）それと
ペイジのエサも忘れないでね！
I'm off!
厳しい人だね…
-He sure is strict.
-Yeah. Around strangers.
（コユキ）他人にはね…
（コユキ）
あ… エサ 俺やるからいいよ
It's okay, I'll feed him.
-He's...
-You little-!
（真帆）こらっ こんのっ
（コユキ）そいつ かむから…
ふんっ これで… 最後だーっ！
T-this is the last of it!
（真帆）
こらっ ああ もう！
うおっ うわぁっ！
（ペイジ）コユキ アホウ！
（コユキ）いたたた…
Oww...
Huh?! What is this?!
These aren't company documents!
うわ！ 何だこれ！
仕事の書類じゃないじゃん！
They're Saito-san's personal treasure!
みんな斎藤さん個人の
お宝じゃないか！
Treasure?
オタカラ？
（コユキ）あ いや… おかず…
I mean, private collection.
ハァ…
（真帆）オカズ…
Collection?
Koyuki, how long have you
been working here?
コユキ
いつから ここで働いてるの？
-Since the end of summer break.
-What for?
夏休みの終わりから
（真帆）何で？
I want to repair the guitar
Ryusuke-kun gave me.
竜介(りゅうすけ)君にもらったギターを
直すためなんだ
I didn't know...
知らなかった
（コユキ）だから ギターが直るまで
竜介君に会いたくないんだ
That's why I don't want to see Ryusuke-kun
until the guitar is fixed.
Right. I understand.
うん 分かった！
で 時給いくら？
（コユキ）う…
So, how much do you get paid?
Oh, umm...430 yen an hour.
よ… 430円
Are you serious?! That's crazy!
（真帆）
え マジ!? 信じらんない…
（ペイジ）グエ～！
ふむ この新法…
製造業には不利な面が多いな
This new law sure is bad
for the manufacturing industry.
（店員）斎藤様 どうぞ
-Saito-sama, this way please.
-Yes.
（斎藤）うむ
Thank you for waiting.
（店員）お待たせしました
Rie-chan! Thank you for calling her.
リエちゃん！
ご指名ありがとうございます
（リエ）あ～っ ケンケンだ～！
リエリエ チョ～寂しかったのぉ～
-Oh, it's Ken-ken!
-Rie-rie!
（斎藤）
あ～ん リエリエ～
-I missed you sooo much!
-Me too!
（リエ）あ～っ ケンケンだ～！
リエリエ チョ～寂しかったのぉ～
（斎藤）
う～ん ぱっくんちょ
（泉(いずみ)）うん？
What's with the get-up?
Caught a cold or something?
何それ？ 風邪でもひいたの？
I'm in disguise! But how'd
you guess it was me?
（コユキ）変装だよ！
もう 何でバレたのかな…
You stand out too much.
Okay, it's starting!
それ目立ちすぎ さあ 始まるぞー！
Ryusuke-kun's guitar...
Are those bullet marks?!
竜介君のギター…
撃たれた跡？
Yup. They're real.
（真帆）うん あれ本物なんだ
（コユキ）それって…
Is that...
That guitar has a name...
It's Lucille.
（真帆）ルシールって名前が
あるんだ あのギター
-Sounds like a woman's name.
-Yeah...
（コユキ）女の人の名前みたい
（真帆）うん…
It's a guitar with a past...
Ryusuke got it in some dangerous place.
竜介がヤバいとこで手に入れた
いわくつきのギター
でも… まさか演奏中に
撃たれたとかじゃ…
But...It couldn't possibly have
happened while he was performing?!
One, two!
（千葉(ちば)）ワン ツー
Typhoon 24! 24-7! 24 hours straight!
BECK! B-E-C-K!
We're gonna rush at you!
We're gonna send you flyin' head-first!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
you'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
You just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot,
keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Squeeze your sweat
This...is Beck...
（コユキ）これが… BECK
Koyuki-kun...
（斎藤）コユキくーん
Can you go over to Hayakama Instruments?
ハヤカマ楽器
行ってきてくれない？
Huh?! There's still more?!
（コユキ）
え～ まだあるんですか？
-The guitar's fixed now.
-Huh?!
ギター 直ったってさ
（コユキ）へ？
The one with the broken neck.
I sent it out for repairs.
あのネックの折れたギターだよ
僕が直しに出しといたんだ
そ… それ ホントですか!?
I-is that true?!
You want to patch things up
with Ryusuke, don't you?
竜介って子と
仲直りしたいんだろ？
あっ 斎藤さん…
Saito-san!
Now go, hurry!
（斎藤）ほら 早く行ってきな
Okay!
（コユキ）はい！
Koyuki-kun...Deduction for leaving early.
コユキ君 早退分 減給っと
I think this'll do.
（店員）
これで一応 問題ないと思うけどね
あと弾いてみて何かあったら
また教えてよ
If you notice something
while playing it, just let me know.
Now I can see Ryusuke-kun!
（コユキ）これで… これで—
竜介君に会える！
（兵藤）おい 田中！
Hey, Tanaka...
Hey, Tanaka. Lemme play that guitar.
おい田中
そのギターちょっと弾かせろよ
Yuck! What an awful sound...
suits you perfectly!
（兵藤）うわっ
お前にお似合いの ひでえ音だな
Hey, Masaru. Lemme try.
（力也(りきや)）
おいマサル ちょっと交代しろよ
What? Forget it, Rikiya-kun.
The sound is the pits.
（兵藤）え～ 力也君
やめといたほうがいいよー
音 サイアク！
You laughed just now, didn't you?
（力也）
お前… 今 笑っただろ？
-Huh?!
-Don't act innocent!
（コユキ）え!?
（力也）とぼけんな！
（コユキ）あ いや… 今の—
No, I thought that tune
was "Anarchy in Heaven"...
「アナーキー・イン・ザ・ヘブン」
かなって…
Recently, the Sex Handles-
俺 最近セックス・ハンドルズに…
（力也）
けっ！ それっ この… でいっ！
Damn thing!
Any complaints?
文句あるか？
ハハハッ そうだよな
こんなボロギター
Didn't think so. It was a
piece of junk anyway. Let's go, Masaru!
行くぞ マサル
（兵藤）ああ
Yeah.
-Let's go grind someplace.
-How about New Burger?
（力也）
さて 飯でも食いに行くかー
（兵藤）
あ ニューバーガー行かね？
（斎藤）
あっ どうだった？ コユキ君
Oh! Did you get it, Koyuki-kun?
Yeah...
Oh, good!
そっかー よかった！
よっと… ちゃんと直ったんだね
It's all fixed, then?
Actually, it's been slow
here at Saito Paper Company,
実は斎藤紙業も なかなか大変でさ
よいしょっ
so getting the money
to fix it was a bit hard.
修理のお金 工面すんの
結構苦労したんだよー
But it was worth it
to see you smiling again!
でも… コユキ君の笑顔が見れて
よかった！
Saito-san...Thank you!
斎藤さん ありがとう
Oh, you're welcome!
いや～！
Mom used to say, "From that day on,
Yukio was like someone
（コユキ）母さんが言っていた…
“幸雄は あの日以来
何かに取りつかれたように—”
possessed by the guitar,
and played it every single day."
“ギターを
毎日弾きまくってる”って
You were great at the concert!
（ファン１）
ライブ サイコーでしたぁ！
（千葉）あ ホント？ ヘヘヘ…
Think so?!
I just looove your vocals, Chiba-kun!
（ファン２）
私な～ 千葉君のボーカル—
めっちゃ好きやねん
（千葉）
アハハ… おっ お～…
We won't miss your next live performance!
（ファン１）ねえ 今度のライブも
絶対行くからねっ
Then I'll put you on the guest list!
Give me your names and numbers!
あ… そんじゃゲストリストに
載せとくからさ—
名前と携帯 教えてよ
ねえ ヘヘヘ…
（ファン２）アハハハ…
Hey, Ray! I've gotta talk to you!
（真帆：英語）〈ねえ 竜介〉
（千葉）ん？
（ファン２）あっ
〈話があるんだ〉
Huh? What?
（竜介：英語）〈何だ？
いきなり来て 何 怒ってんだ？〉
What're you mad about all of a sudden?
Wow! Ryusuke-kun, you speak English!
（ファン１）わぁーっ
竜介君って英語話せるんだー
That's so cool!
（ファン２）すっごーい！
Yeah. I lived in New York for a long time.
（竜介）あー 俺 ニューヨーク
長かったから—
So I'm more used to English than Japanese.
日本語より英語のほうが楽なんだよ
（ファン１）ウフッ
-That's so cool!
（ファンたち）カッコいー！
We've got to go to New York, too!
（ファン２）うちらも今度
ニューヨーク遊びに行くんよ！
-Tell us where you used to live!
-Yeah! We wanna visit it!
（ファン１）竜介君の
住んでた場所 教えてよ！
（ファン２）
あっ そーやぁ 見てきたいわ
（ファン１）
ねえ 教えて～
（竜介）ああ いいよ
（ファン１）やった 嬉しー！
-Sure.
-Yay!
（ファン２）ありがと～
Those idiots!
バカどもめが…
I was looking for the ab machine
I bought by mail order last night...
（真帆）〈腹筋鍛えようかなって
思ってさ 機械捜してたら—〉
and I finally found it!
〈見つけたんだ！〉
Found what?
（竜介）〈見つけた？ 何を？〉
Look!
〈これだよ！〉
This is it...The L48 Eddie gave to you!
〈これ エディからもらった
Ｌ48じゃん！〉
Huh? Then the one I gave to Koyuki was...
〈え!? それじゃ 俺が
コユキにやったのは〉
That was a fake one you got
at the guitar shop in Queens!
〈竜介がクイーンズで手に入れた
偽物だよ〉
Which means...
てことは… わぁっ！
（ファンたち）
ああっ！ 竜介君！
-Ryusuke-kun!
ハハハハ！
破傷風に気ぃつけろよー！
Don't get tetanus!
Yukio! Telephone!
（コユキの母）幸雄～ 電話よー
Yukio! Yukio!
幸雄！
幸雄ー！
I called Ryusuke too.
（真帆）でさ 竜介も呼んだから
You're joking, right?
ウソ… でしょ？
Oh, speak of the devil.
お… ウワサの主だ
（竜介・真帆）あっ
（コユキ）ごめん！
Sorry!
Maho...Did you really explain it to him?
〈真帆!? ちゃんとコユキに
説明したのか？〉
I did!
〈もちろん！〉
（コユキ）ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
Idiot! Why am I running away?!
（コユキ）バカだ…
俺 何で逃げてんだ？
Oh, Koyuki!
（泉）あーっ コユキ～！
Izumi-chan!
（コユキ）泉ちゃん！
I spoke to Ryusuke-kun on the phone
yesterday and he said to say hi.
きのう ちょっと
電話で話したんだけど—
竜介君がコユキによろしくってさ
Oh...Can you say hello from me, too?
じゃあ 俺からもよろしくって…
All 9th graders will report
to the gym for curriculum guidance.
（アナウンス）
進路指導があるので—
３年生は体育館に集合してください
I repeat...
放送 繰り返します…
-It's almost graduation.
-Yeah...
（コユキ）もうすぐ卒業なんだね
（泉）そうだね
I'll be lonely.
（コユキ）寂しくなるなぁ
Really?
ホント？
See you, Koyuki!
じゃーね コユキ！
ハァ…
"Dear Koyuki-kun,"
"I've decided to stay here a bit longer,
so please take care of Page!"
He's extending his stay again!
（コユキ）また滞在延長か～
Southeast Asia must have
something that lures grown men...
東南アジアには—
大人の男を引き寄せる
何かがあるらしい…
Fool!
（ペイジ）アホーッ
I haven't played yet!
（コユキ）まだ弾いてないぞ
Punk rockers hold their guitars low...
パンクの人って
ギター低めに構えるんだよな…
Awright!
よーし！
Yay!
（コユキ）イェーイ！
Cripes! I'd better go to sleep!
ヤッベー 寝ないと…
"Kugatsu no Umi wa Darui Hito"
（東郷(とうごう)）み 見てみな…
（竜介）ん？
Look...
Eiji...
栄二(えいじ)…
Look at him...
（東郷）やな感じだな
（東郷）あいつのバンド
ワンマン成功させたんだろ？
Didn't he make his band successful
all by himself?
We just do things our way.
俺たちは自分らのやり方で
いくだけさ
Umm...Ginger ale.
（真帆）えーと ジンジャーエール
Okay.
（店員）ジンジャー
Hey, Koyuki! Why'd you
run away the other day?!
おい コユキ！
この前 何で逃げた!?
Sorry!
（コユキ）ごめん！
（千葉）イェー！ オウ！
Koyuki! Let's go up front!
（真帆）コユキ 前 行くよ！
（千葉）
よう チェックしろ！
Let's go concrete hell,
human safari park escape
Ape in the brain,
mass brain-washing operation,
no thank you
Let's walk together, step in step,
and we'll get stuck in the deep
ラップって… こんなに…
-I-is this what rap is?
-Let's walk together, step in step,
and we'll get stuck in the deep
-I-is this what rap is?
-We're at the rebellious age,
free as we go
（真帆）えっ？
コユキ 何か言った？
-Huh? You say something?
-We're at the rebellious age,
free as we go
This is no barrier, just what is important,
nothing impure, just clear
No pressure at our pace
Who? Who? Foojin
Takes me cruisin'
Music that cuts through the wind,
free form
（栄二(えいじ)）うん？
ボディーに弾痕…
Bullet holes in the body...
That's a creepy guitar...
まったく不気味なギターだぜ
The acoustic pick-up
in the front is broken.
フロントピックアップが
壊れてるのか？
He has a Roger Mayer at his feet.
足元にはロジャー・メイヤー…
But...How is he getting such a sound?
なのに… 何でこんな音が…
Wow! Amazing!
（ファン２）お～ すっご～い！
-Hey, look at that poster!
-I'm gonna get a shot of it!
（ファン１）
ね あの看板見てよ カッコいい～！
（ファン２）
おー じゃあ あれも撮っとこ
（ファン１）ねっ！
（ファン２）よいしょっ
（ファン２）
ええもん撮れた～ ハハハッ
So this is where Ryusuke-kun
grew up! Isn't it cool!
（ファン２）竜介君の育った街って
やっぱ 何かいいよね～
Totally!
（ファン１）ね～！ ウフフッ！
Huh?
（ファン２）あれ…
（ファン１）ん？
That dog...
あの犬って…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Cuttlefish...
（千葉）イカのワタ焼き
マツタケの炭火焼き…
Grilled matsutake mushrooms...
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Grilled matsutake mushrooms...
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Mackerel...Eggplant, shortcake...
サンマ ナス
ショートケーキ…
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Eat it all!
食いね～っ！